Occasionally, you'll end up with a data set that has
في بعض الأحيان، ستنتهي بمجموعة بيانات
some nulls that you'd prefer to contain actual values.
تحتوي على بعض القيم الخالية التي تفضل أن تحتوي على قيم فعلية.
Looking at the accounts table,
بالنظر إلى جدول الحسابات،
you might want to clearly label a no primary point of contact as no POC,
قد ترغب في تسمية نقطة اتصال أساسية بشكل واضح على أنها ليست POC،
so the results will be easily understandable.
لذلك ستكون النتائج سهلة الفهم.
In cases like this, you can use coalesce to replace the null values.
في حالات مثل هذه، يمكنك استخدام التجميع لاستبدال القيم الخالية.
This is something you may want to do frequently when using
هذا أمر قد ترغب في القيام به بشكل متكرر عند استخدام
numerical data where you might want to display nulls as zero.
البيانات الرقمية حيثما ترغب في عرض القيم الخالية على أنها صفر.
Also, when performing outer joins that result in some unmatched rows,
أيضًا، عند إجراء عمليات الربط الخارجي التي تؤدي إلى بعض الصفوف غير المتطابقة،
you may want those unmatched rows to display something other than a null value.
قد ترغب في أن تعرض هذه الصفوف غير المتطابقة لتعرض شيئًا آخر بخلاف القيمة الخالية.
Of course, this is most valuable when working with a function that treats
بالطبع، هذا هو الأكثر قيمة عند العمل مع دالة تعامل القيم الخالية
nulls differently from zero such as a count or an average.
بشكل مختلف عن الصفر مثل العد أو المتوسط.
We can demonstrate this by wrapping the coalesce in
يمكننا أن نوضح ذلك من خلال التفاف التجميع
a count function and counting the primary POC column without the coalesce, as well.
في دالة العد وإحصاء عمود نقطة اتصال رئيسية دون التجميع، كذلك.
As you can see, the count that includes the coalesce,
كما ترى، يشتمل العد الذي يتضمن التجمّيع على
includes nine more results than the other regular
تسع نتائج أخرى أكثر من النتائج العادية الأخرى